[{
    "id": 1,
    "points": 1,
    "question": "What is an individual unit of a blockchain?",
    "correct_answer": "Block",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Bitcoin", "Satoshi","BIP"
    ]
},{
    "id": 2,
    "points": 10,
    "question": "The process by which transactions are verified and added to a blockchain is known as:",
    "correct_answer": "Mining",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Smart Contracts", "Batching","Cryptography"
    ]
},{
    "id": 3,
    "points": 100,
    "question": "A type of digital currency, without a central bank or single administrator, that can be sent from user to user without the need for intermediaries.",
    "correct_answer": "Bitcoin",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Shitcoin", "Blockchain","Node"
    ]
},{
    "id": 4,
    "points": 1000,
    "question": "A measurement of the processing power of the Bitcoin network is called:",
    "correct_answer": "Hash Rate",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Block Chain", "Satoshi","Margin Trading"
    ]
},{
    "id": 5,
    "points": 100000,
    "question": "The Bitcoin algorithm is programmed to self-adjust every 2,016 blocks. This process is known as:",
    "correct_answer": "Difficulty Adjustment",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Halving Cycle", "Digital Signature","Mining"
    ]
},{
    "id": 6,
    "points": 10000000,
    "question": "The pseudonymous creator of Bitcoin whose real-world identity remains unknown.",
    "correct_answer": "Satoshi Nakamoto",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Satoshi Bitnato", "Pas Meekhunsut","Ruja Ignatova"
    ]
},{
    "id": 7,
    "points": 100000000,
    "question": "Also known as a SAT, this is one hundred-millionth of a bitcoin, or the smallest unit of the currency that can possibly be sent on the blockchain.",
    "correct_answer": "Satoshi",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dogecoin", "Seed","Shitcoin"
    ]
},{
    "id": 8,
    "points": 1000000000,
    "question": "When the reward for mining bitcoin transactions is cut in half.",
    "correct_answer": "Halving",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Hard Fork", "Hashing", "Halfsies"
    ]
},{
    "id": 9,
    "points": 100000000000,
    "question": "A digital record of transactions where the name comes from its structure, in which individual records are linked together in single list.",
    "correct_answer": "Block Chain",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Bit Chain", "Block Coin", "Block Head"
    ]
},{
    "id": 10,
    "points": 100000000000,
    "question": "Block size in bitcoin refers to the size of a block of code representing a recent chain of bitcoin transactions. A block contains more than 500 transactions on average. How large is a Block size?",
    "correct_answer": "1 Megabyte",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "1 Gigabyte", "1 Terrabyte", "1 BitByte"
    ]
},{
    "id": 11,
    "points": 101010101001,
    "question": "What is the best tool to make cool web apps?",
    "correct_answer": "Svelte",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "React", "Vue", "PHP"
    ]
}]
